The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Global	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	global	O
Seed	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	seed	O
Vault	NNP	N[nam]	vault	O
opened	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	open	O
near	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	near	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
North	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	north	I-LOC
Pole	NNP	N[nam]	pole	I-LOC
on	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	on	O
26	CD	N[nam]/N[nam]	26	I-DAT
February	NNP	N[nam]	february	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]\S[dcl]/S[dcl]\S[dcl]	,	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
Internet	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	internet	O
project	NN	N[nom]	project	O
aimed	VBN	S[pss]\NP/PP	aim	O
at	IN	PP/S[ng]\NP	at	O
promoting	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	promote	O
biodiversity	NN	N[nom]	biodiversity	O
went	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP	go	O
on	IN	PP/NP	on	O
line	NN	N[nom]	line	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
so-called	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	so-called	O
"	LQU	N[nom]/N[nom]	"	O
doomsday	NN	N[nom]	doomsday	O
"	RQU	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	"	O
vault	NN	N[nom]	vault	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/PP	be	O
in	IN	PP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
remote	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	remote	O
Norwegian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	norwegian	O
archipelago	NN	N[nom]	archipelago	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Svalbard	NNP	N[nam]	svalbard	I-LOC
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
designed	VBN	S[pss]\NP/S[to]\NP	design	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
protect	VB	S[b]\NP/PP/NP	protect	O
millions	NNS	N[nom]	million	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
seeds	NNS	N[nom]	seed	O
from	IN	PP/NP	from	O
climate	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	climate	O
change	NN	N[nom]	change	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
other	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	other	O
disasters	NNS	N[nom]	disaster	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Encyclopedia	NNP	N[nam]	encyclopedia	I-ORG
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	I-ORG
Life	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	life	I-ORG
web	NNP	N[nam]	web	I-ORG
siteis	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	sitei	O
just	RB	NP/NP	just	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
click	NN	N[nom]	click	O
away	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	away	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
meant	VBN	S[pss]\NP/PP	mean	O
as	IN	PP/NP	as	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
source	NN	N[nom]	source	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
information	NN	N[nom]	information	O
about	IN	NP\NP/NP	about	O
all	DT	NP/N[nom]	all	O
living	VBG	N[nom]/N[nom]	live	O
things	NNS	N[nom]	thing	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	O
Paul	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	paul	I-PER
Sisco	NNP	N[nam]	sisco	I-PER
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	have	O
more	RBR	N[nom]	more	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



