Five-time	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	five-time	O
Olympic	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	olympic	O
champion	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	champion	O
Ian	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	ian	I-PER
Thorpe	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	thorpe	I-PER
's	POS	N[nom]	's	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Australia	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	australium	I-LOC
return	NN	N[nom]	return	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
competitive	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	competitive	O
swimming	NN	N[nom]	swimming	O
after	IN	NP\NP/NP	after	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
15-month	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	15-month	O
break	NN	N[nom]	break	O
lasted	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	last	O
only	RB	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	only	O
one	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	one	O
race	NN	N[nom]	race	O
at	IN	NP\NP/NP	at	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
World	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	world	I-ORG
Cup	NNP	N[nam]	cup	I-ORG
meet	VB	S[b]\NP	meet	O
in	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	in	O
Sydney	NNP	N[nam]	sydney	I-LOC
.	.	S[b]\S[b]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Australian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	australian	O
star	NN	N[nom]	star	O
withdrew	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	withdraw	O
from	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	from	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
event	NN	N[nom]	event	O
Saturday	NNP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	saturday	I-DAT
due	JJ	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	due	O
to	TO	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	to	O
illness	NN	N[nom]	illness	O
after	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	after	O
clocking	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	clock	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
fastest	JJS	N[nom]/N[nom]	fastest	O
time	NN	N[nom]	time	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
qualifying	VBG	N[nom]/N[nom]	qualify	O
race	NN	N[nom]	race	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
men	NNS	N[nom]	man	O
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
100-meter	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	100-meter	I-DAT
freestyle	NN	N[nom]	freestyle	I-DAT
earlier	RBR	NP\NP/PP	earlier	I-DAT
in	IN	PP/NP	in	I-DAT
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	I-DAT
day	NN	N[nom]	day	I-DAT
(	LRB	NP\NP/NP	(	O
47.87	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	47.87	I-TIM
seconds	NNS	N[nom]	seconds	I-TIM
)	RRB	NP\NP\NP\NP	)	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Australia	NNP	N[nam]	australium	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
coach	NN	N[nom]	coach	O
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
Alan	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	alan	I-PER
Thompson	NNP	N[nam]	thompson	I-PER
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
Thorpe	NNP	N[nam]	thorpe	I-PER
had	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
not	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	not	O
been	VBN	S[pt]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
feeling	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[adj]\NP	feel	O
well	RB	S[adj]\NP	well	O
all	DT	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP/N[nom]	all	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	,	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
had	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
missed	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	miss	O
some	DT	NP/N[nom]	some	O
training	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	training	O
sessions	NNS	N[nom]	session	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Thorpe	NNP	N[nam]	thorpe	I-PER
took	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	take	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
extended	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	extended	O
break	NN	N[nom]	break	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
competition	NN	N[nom]	competition	O
following	VBG	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	follow	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
2004	CD	N[nam]/N[nam]	2004	I-DAT
Athens	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	athen	I-LOC
Olympics	NNPS	N[nam]	olympics	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



