Russia	NNP	N[nam]	russium	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
minister	NN	N[nom]	minister	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
halting	VBG	S[ng]\NP/PP/NP	halt	O
aid	NN	N[nom]	aid	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Hamas-led	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	hamas-led	O
Palestinian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	palestinian	O
government	NN	N[nom]	government	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
mistake	NN	N[nom]	mistake	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Sergei	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	sergeus	I-PER
Lavrov	NNP	N[nam]	lavrov	I-PER
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
comments	NNS	N[nom]	comment	O
Tuesday	NNP	NP\NP	tuesday	I-DAT
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Moscow	NNP	N[nam]	moscow	I-LOC
came	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	come	O
just	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	just	O
days	NNS	N[nom]	day	O
after	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP\NP/S[dcl]	after	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
United	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	united	I-LOC
States	NNPS	N[nam]	state	I-LOC
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
European	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	european	I-ORG
Union	NNP	N[nam]	union	I-ORG
suspended	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	suspend	O
direct	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	direct	O
aid	NN	N[nom]	aid	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Palestinian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	palestinian	O
government	NN	N[nom]	government	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Lavrov	NNP	N[nam]	lavrov	I-PER
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
funding	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	funding	O
cut-off	NN	N[nom]	cut-off	O
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
only	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	only	O
serve	VB	S[b]\NP/S[to]\NP	serve	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
further	RBR	S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP	further	O
destabilize	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	destabilize	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
region	NN	N[nom]	region	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

He	PRP	NP	he	O
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
only	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	only	O
way	NN	N[nom]	way	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
ensure	VB	S[b]\NP/S[em]	ensure	O
that	IN	S[em]/S[dcl]	that	O
Hamas	NNP	N[nam]	hama	I-LOC
meets	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	meet	O
Western	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	western	I-ORG
demands	NNS	N[nom]	demand	I-ORG
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[to]\NP	be	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
engage	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	engage	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Hamas	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	hama	I-LOC
leadership	NN	N[nom]	leadership	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT		the	O
U.S.	NNP		u.s.	I-LOC
and	CC		and	O
EU	NNP		eu	I-ORG
are	VBP		be	O
demanding	VBG		demand	O
that	IN		that	O
Hamas	NNP		hama	I-LOC
renounce	NN		renounce	O
terrorism	NN		terrorism	O
and	CC		and	O
recognize	VB		recognize	O
Israel	NNP		israel	I-LOC
's	POS		's	O
right	NN		right	O
to	TO		to	O
exist	VB		exist	O
.	.		.	O



