With	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	with	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Democratic	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	democratic	I-ORG
National	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	national	I-ORG
Convention	NNP	N[nam]	convention	I-ORG
ending	VBG	S[ng]\NP	end	O
this	DT	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP/N[nom]	this	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Republicans	NNPS	N[nam]	republican	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
follow	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	follow	O
next	JJ	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	next	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
those	DT	NP/N[nom]	those	O
efforts	NNS	N[nom]	effort	O
have	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
switched	VBN	S[pt]\NP/PP	switch	O
into	IN	PP/NP	into	O
high	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	high	O
gear	NN	N[nom]	gear	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



