Nepal	NNP	N[nam]	nepal	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
government	NN	N[nom]	government	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
non-	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	non-	O
profit	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	profit	O
World	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	world	I-ORG
Wildlife	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	wildlife	I-ORG
fund	NN	N[nom]	fund	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
launching	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	launch	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
new	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	new	O
appeal	NN	N[nom]	appeal	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
save	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	save	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
critically	RB	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	critically	O
endangered	VBN	N[nom]/N[nom]	endanger	O
one-horned	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	one-horned	I-DAT
rhino	NN	N[nom]	rhino	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Paul	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	paul	I-PER
Sisco	NNP	N[nam]	sisco	I-PER
reports	VBZ	S[dcl]\S[dcl]\NP	report	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]\S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



