An	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
Israeli	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	israeli	O
official	NN	N[nom]	official	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
Israel	NNP	N[nam]	israel	I-LOC
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
considering	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	consider	O
plans	NNS	N[nom]	plan	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
build	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	build	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
nuclear	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	nuclear	O
power	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	power	O
station	NN	N[nom]	station	O
in	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	in	O
its	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	its	O
southern	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	southern	O
Negev	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	negev	I-LOC
desert	NN	N[nom]	desert	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Israel	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	israel	I-LOC
Army	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	army	I-ORG
Radio	NNP	N[nam]	radio	I-ORG
quoted	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP/NP	quote	O
Infrastructure	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	infrastructure	O
Minister	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	minister	O
Binyamin	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	binyamin	I-PER
Ben-Elizer	NNP	N[nam]	ben-elizer	I-PER
as	IN	PP/S[ng]\NP	as	O
saying	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
he	PRP	NP	he	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	have	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
support	NN	N[nom]	support	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Prime	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	prime	O
Minister	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	minister	O
Ehud	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	ehud	I-PER
Olmert	NNP	N[nam]	olmert	I-PER
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
that	IN	NP\NP/S[dcl]	that	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
plan	NN	N[nom]	plan	O
would	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	would	O
be	VB	S[b]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
considered	VBN	S[pss]\NP	consider	O
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
coming	VBG	N[nom]/N[nom]	come	O
months	NNS	N[nom]	month	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
construction	NN	N[nom]	construction	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
nuclear	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	nuclear	O
power	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	power	O
plant	NN	N[nom]	plant	O
could	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	could	O
draw	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	draw	O
renewed	VBN	N[nom]/N[nom]	renew	O
attention	NN	N[nom]	attention	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
what	WP	NP/S[dcl]\NP	what	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
widely	RB	S[pss]\NP/S[pss]\NP	widely	O
believed	VBN	S[pss]\NP/S[to]\NP	believe	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
be	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	be	O
Israel	NNP	N[nam]	israel	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
nuclear	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	nuclear	O
weapons	NNS	N[nom]/N[nom]	weapon	O
program	NN	N[nom]	program	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Following	VBG	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	follow	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
policy	NN	N[nom]	policy	O
that	IN	NP\NP/S[dcl]/NP	that	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
calls	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP/NP	call	O
"	LQU	NP/NP	"	O
nuclear	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	nuclear	O
ambiguity	NN	N[nom]	ambiguity	O
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
"	LQU	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	"	O
Israel	NNP	N[nam]	israel	I-LOC
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
never	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	never	O
admitted	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	admit	O
nor	CC	CONJ	nor	O
denied	VBN	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	deny	O
having	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	have	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
nuclear	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	nuclear	O
weapons	NNS	N[nom]/N[nom]	weapon	O
program	NN	N[nom]	program	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



