The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Siboney	NNP	N[nam]	siboney	I-ORG
were	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
first	JJ	N[nom]	first	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
inhabit	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	inhabit	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
islands	NNS	N[nom]	island	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Antigua	NNP	N[nam]	antigua	I-LOC
and	CC	CONJ	and	I-ORG
Barbuda	NNP	N[nam]	barbuda	I-LOC
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
2400	CD	N[nam]/N[nam]	2400	I-DAT
B.C.,	NNP	N[nam]	b.c.,	I-DAT
but	CC	CONJ	but	O
Arawak	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	arawak	I-ORG
Indians	NNPS	N[nam]	indian	I-ORG
populated	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	populate	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
islands	NNS	N[nom]	island	O
when	WRB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	when	O
COLUMBUS	NNS	N[nom]	columbus	O
landed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	land	O
on	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	on	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
second	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	second	O
voyage	NN	N[nom]	voyage	O
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
1493	CD	N[num]	1493	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Early	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	early	O
settlements	NNS	N[nom]	settlement	O
by	IN	NP\NP/NP	by	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Spanish	JJ	N[nom]	spanish	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
French	JJ	N[nom]	french	O
were	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
succeeded	VBN	S[pss]\NP	succeed	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
English	NNP	N[nam]	english	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
formed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	form	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
colony	NN	N[nom]	colony	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
1667	CD	N[num]	1667	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Slavery	NNP	N[nam]	slavery	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
established	VBD	S[pss]\NP	establish	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
run	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	run	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
sugar	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	sugar	O
plantations	NNS	N[nom]	plantation	O
on	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	on	O
Antigua	NNP	N[nam]	antigua	I-LOC
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
abolished	VBN	S[pss]\NP	abolish	O
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
1834	CD	N[num]	1834	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
islands	NNS	N[nom]	island	O
became	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	become	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
independent	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	independent	O
state	NN	N[nom]	state	O
within	IN	NP\NP/NP	within	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
British	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	british	I-ORG
Commonwealth	NNP	N[nam]	commonwealth	I-ORG
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	I-ORG
Nations	NNPS	N[nam]	nation	I-ORG
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
1981	CD	N[num]	1981	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



