Russia	NNP	N[nam]	russium	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
minister	NN	N[nom]	minister	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
Iraq	NNP	N[nam]	iraq	I-LOC
could	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	could	O
split	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	split	O
into	IN	PP/NP	into	O
different	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	different	O
states	NNS	N[nom]	state	O
if	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/S[dcl]	if	O
its	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	its	O
ethnic	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	ethnic	O
groups	NNS	N[nom]	group	O
fail	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[to]\NP	fail	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
unite	VB	S[b]\NP	unite	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Russia	NNP	N[nam]	russium	I-LOC
opposed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	oppose	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
U.S.-led	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.-led	O
invasion	NN	N[nom]	invasion	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Iraq	NNP	N[nam]	iraq	I-LOC
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
2003	CD	N[num]	2003	I-DAT
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
called	VBN	S[pt]\NP/PP	call	O
for	IN	PP/NP	for	O
efforts	NNS	N[nom]	effort	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
contain	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	contain	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
violence	NN	N[nom]	violence	O
there	RB	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	there	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



