This	DT	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/N[nom]	this	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
United	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	united	I-ORG
Nations	NNPS	N[nam]	nation	I-ORG
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
expected	VBN	S[pss]\NP/S[to]\NP	expect	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
issue	VB	S[b]\NP/PP/NP	issue	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
appeal	NN	N[nom]	appeal	O
for	IN	PP/NP	for	O
up	RB	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	up	O
to	TO	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	to	O
40	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	40	I-MON
million	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	million	I-MON
dollars	NNS	N[nom]	dollar	I-MON
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
help	VB	S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP/NP	help	O
Somalia	NNP	N[nam]	somalium	I-LOC
recover	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	recover	O
from	IN	PP/NP	from	O
last	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	last	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
’s	NNS	N[nom]	’s	I-DAT
tsunami	VBP	S[dcl]\S[dcl]\NP	tsunami	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
latest	JJS	N[nom]/N[nom]	latest	O
death	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	death	O
toll	NN	N[nom]	toll	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Somalia	NNP	N[nam]	somalium	I-LOC
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/PP	be	O
around	IN	PP/NP	around	O
140	CD	N[num]	140	O
,	,	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	,	O
according	VBG	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/PP	accord	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
figures	NNS	N[nom]	figure	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
transitional	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	transitional	O
government	NN	N[nom]	government	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Elballa	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	elballum	I-ORG
Hagona	NNP	N[nam]	hagona	I-ORG
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Acting	VBG	N[nam]/N[nam]	act	O
UN	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	un	I-ORG
Humanitarian	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	humanitarian	I-ORG
Coordinator	NNP	N[nam]	coordinator	I-ORG
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	I-ORG
Somalia	NNP	N[nam]	somalium	I-ORG
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

From	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	from	O
Nairobi	NNP	N[nam]	nairobus	I-LOC
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
he	PRP	NP	he	O
told	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[em]/NP	tell	O
English	NNP	N[nam]	english	I-ORG
to	TO	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	to	O
Africa	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	africa	I-LOC
reporter	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	reporter	O
Joe	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	joe	I-ORG
De	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	de	I-ORG
Capua	NNP	N[nam]	capua	I-ORG
that	IN	S[em]/S[dcl]	that	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
assessment	NN	N[nom]	assessment	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
country	NN	N[nom]	country	O
continues	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP	continue	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
final	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	final	O
report	NN	N[nom]	report	O
should	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	should	O
be	VB	S[b]\NP/S[adj]\NP	be	O
available	JJ	S[adj]\NP	available	O
in	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	in	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	I-DAT
few	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	few	I-DAT
days	NNS	N[nom]	day	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



