An	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
Australian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	australian	O
archaeology	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	archaeology	O
team	NN	N[nom]	team	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
located	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	locate	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
ancient	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	ancient	O
Egyptian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	egyptian	O
city	NN	N[nom]	city	O
used	VBN	S[pss]\NP	use	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
occupiers	NNS	N[nom]	occupier	O
some	DT	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	some	O
3,500	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	3,500	I-DAT
years	NNS	N[nom]	year	I-DAT
ago	RB	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP\NP	ago	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Egypt	NNP	N[nam]	egypt	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
antiquities	NNS	N[nom]/N[nom]	antiquity	O
department	NN	N[nom]	department	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
pictures	NNS	N[nom]	picture	O
taken	VBN	S[pss]\NP	take	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
radar	NN	N[nom]	radar	O
show	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/NP	show	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
underground	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	underground	O
city	NN	N[nom]	city	O
complete	JJ	S[adj]\NP/PP	complete	O
with	IN	PP/NP	with	O
streets	NNS	N[nom]	street	O
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
houses	NNS	N[nom]	house	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
temples	NNS	N[nom]	temple	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

It	PRP	NP	it	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
located	VBN	S[pss]\NP	locate	O
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
area	NN	N[nom]	area	O
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
Egypt	NNP	N[nam]	egypt	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	I-ORG
Nile	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	nile	I-ORG
Delta	NNP	N[nam]	delta	I-ORG
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Antiquities	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	antiquity	O
Chief	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	chief	O
Zahi	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	zahus	I-PER
Hawass	NNP	N[nam]	hawass	I-PER
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
ancient	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	ancient	O
city	NN	N[nom]	city	O
could	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	could	O
be	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	be	O
part	NN	N[nom]	part	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Avaris	NNP	N[nam]	avari	I-ORG
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
capital	NN	N[nom]	capital	O
used	VBN	S[pss]\NP	use	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Hyksos	NNP	N[nam]	hykso	I-LOC
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
Asiatic	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	asiatic	O
group	NN	N[nom]	group	O
that	WDT	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	that	O
ruled	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	rule	O
Egypt	NNP	N[nam]	egypt	I-ORG
from	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	from	O
1664	CD	N[num]	1664	I-DAT
through	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	through	I-DAT
1569	CD	N[nam]/N[nam]	1569	I-DAT
BC	NNP	N[nam]	bc	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



