Organizers	NNS	N[nom]	organizer	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
vote	NN	N[nom]	vote	O
by	IN	NP\NP/NP	by	O
Iraqi	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	iraqus	O
expatriates	NNS	N[nom]	expatriate	O
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
some	DT	NP/N[nom]	some	O
two-thirds	NNS	N[nom]	two-third	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
eligable	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	eligable	O
Iraqis	NNS	N[nom]	iraqi	O
living	VBG	S[ng]\NP	live	O
abroad	RB	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP	abroad	O
have	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
participated	VBN	S[pt]\NP	participate	O
in	IN	S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
historic	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	historic	O
election	NN	N[nom]	election	O
so	RB	S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP/S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP	so	O
far	RB	S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP	far	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
International	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	international	I-ORG
Organization	NNP	N[nam]	organization	I-ORG
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	I-ORG
Migration	NNP	N[nam]	migration	I-ORG
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
Sunday	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	sunday	I-DAT
more	JJR	S[adj]\NP	more	I-DAT
than	IN	N[nam]/N[nam]/N[nam]/N[nam]\S[adj]\NP	than	I-DAT
186,000	CD	N[nam]/N[nam]	186,000	I-DAT
Iraqis	NNPS	N[nam]	iraqi	I-DAT
voted	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	vote	I-DAT
Friday	NNP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	friday	I-DAT
and	CC	CONJ	and	I-DAT
Saturday	NNP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	saturday	I-DAT
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Middle	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	middle	I-LOC
East	NNP	N[nam]	east	I-LOC
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
North	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	north	I-LOC
America	NNP	N[nam]	america	I-LOC
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
Australia	NNP	N[nam]	australium	I-LOC
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
Western	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	western	I-LOC
Europe	NNP	N[nam]	europe	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT		the	O
three-day	JJ		three-day	I-DAT
process	NN		process	O
runs	VBZ		run	O
until	IN		until	O
the	DT		the	I-DAT
end	NN		end	I-DAT
of	IN		of	I-DAT
Sunday	NNP		sunday	I-DAT
across	IN		across	O
36	CD		36	O
cities	NNS		city	O
in	IN		in	O
14	CD		14	O
nations	NNS		nation	O
,	,		,	O
including	VBG		include	O
Australia	NNP		australium	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Britain	NNP		britain	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Canada	NNP		canada	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Denmark	NNP		denmark	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
France	NNP		france	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Germany	NNP		germany	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Iran	NNP		iran	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Jordan	NNP		jordan	I-PER
,	,		,	O
the	DT		the	O
Netherlands	NNP		netherland	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Sweden	NNP		sweden	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Syria	NNP		syrium	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
Turkey	NNP		turkey	I-LOC
,	,		,	O
United	NNP		united	I-ORG
Arab	NNP		arab	I-ORG
Emirates	NNPS		emirate	I-ORG
and	CC		and	O
the	DT		the	O
United	NNP		united	I-LOC
States	NNPS		state	I-LOC
.	.		.	O



