Eddie	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	eddie	I-PER
Van	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	van	I-PER
Halen	NNP	N[nam]	halen	I-PER
plans	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[to]\NP	plan	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
enter	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	enter	O
rehab	NN	N[nom]	rehab	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

In	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	in	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	I-DAT
March	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	march	I-DAT
8	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	8	I-DAT
statement	NN	N[nom]	statement	O
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
guitarist	NN	N[nom]	guitarist	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
hard	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	hard	O
rock	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	rock	O
band	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	band	O
Van	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	van	I-PER
Halen	NNP	N[nam]	halen	I-PER
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
he	PRP	NP	he	O
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
seek	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	seek	O
treatment	NN	N[nom]	treatment	O
for	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	for	O
unspecified	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	unspecified	O
reasons	NNS	N[nom]	reason	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

He	PRP	NP	he	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
he	PRP	NP	he	O
presently	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	presently	O
feels	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	feel	O
incapable	JJ	S[adj]\NP/PP	incapable	O
of	IN	PP/S[ng]\NP	of	O
giving	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP/NP	give	O
fans	NNS	N[nom]	fan	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
best	JJS	N[nom]/N[nom]	best	O
performance	NN	N[nom]	performance	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

It	PRP	NP	it	O
's	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[qem]/S[adj]\NP	be	O
not	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	not	O
known	VBN	S[adj]\NP	know	O
whether	IN	S[qem]/S[dcl]	whether	O
Eddie	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	eddie	I-PER
Van	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	van	I-PER
Halen	NNP	N[nam]	halen	I-PER
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
be	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	be	O
in	IN	PP/NP	in	O
New	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	new	I-LOC
York	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	york	I-LOC
City	NNP	N[nam]	city	I-LOC
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
Van	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	van	I-PER
Halen	NNP	N[nam]	halen	I-PER
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
March	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	march	I-DAT
12	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	12	I-DAT
induction	NN	N[nom]	induction	O
into	IN	NP\NP/NP	into	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Rock	NNP	N[nam]	rock	I-PER
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
Roll	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	roll	I-PER
Hall	NNP	N[nam]	hall	I-PER
Of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Fame	NNP	N[nam]	fame	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



