Witnesses	NNS	N[nom]	witness	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Somalia	NNP	N[nam]	somalium	I-LOC
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
brother	NN	N[nom]	brother	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
country	NN	N[nom]	country	O
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
deputy	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	deputy	O
prime	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	prime	O
minister	NN	N[nom]	minister	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
been	VBN	S[pt]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
shot	VBN	S[pss]\NP	shoot	O
dead	JJ	S[adj]\NP	dead	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
government	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	government	O
forces	NNS	N[nom]	force	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
witnesses	NNS	N[nom]	witness	O
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
brother	NN	N[nom]	brother	O
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
Abukar	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	abukar	I-PER
Abdisalam	NNP	N[nam]	abdisalam	I-PER
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
talking	VBG	S[ng]\NP/PP	talk	O
on	IN	PP/NP	on	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
mobile	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	mobile	O
phone	NN	N[nom]	phone	O
outside	IN	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP/NP	outside	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
home	NN	N[nom]	home	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
capital	NN	N[nom]	capital	O
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
Mogadishu	NNP	N[nam]	mogadishu	I-LOC
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
when	WRB	NP\NP/S[dcl]	when	O
government	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	government	O
troops	NNS	N[nom]	troops	O
became	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	become	O
suspicious	JJ	S[adj]\NP	suspicious	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
chased	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	chase	O
him	PRP	NP	him	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
shot	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	shoot	O
him	PRP	NP	him	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Abdisalam	NNP	N[nam]	abdisalam	I-PER
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
brother	NN	N[nom]	brother	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Ahmed	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	ahmed	I-ORG
Abdisalam	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	abdisalam	I-PER
Adan	NNP	N[nam]	adan	I-PER
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
also	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	also	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
country	NN	N[nom]	country	O
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
information	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	information	O
minister	NN	N[nom]	minister	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
motive	NN	N[nom]	motive	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
shooting	NN	N[nom]	shooting	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	be	O
unclear	JJ	S[adj]\NP	unclear	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



