New	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	new	I-LOC
York	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	york	I-LOC
City	NNP	N[nam]	city	I-LOC
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
among	IN	NP\NP/NP	among	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
most	RBS	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	most	O
aggressive	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	aggressive	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.	I-LOC
municipalities	NNS	N[nom]	municipality	O
in	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	in	O
pursuing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	pursue	O
new	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	new	O
public	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	public	O
health	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	health	O
regulations	NNS	N[nom]	regulation	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
doing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	do	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
again	RB	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP	again	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

In	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	in	O
2003	CD	N[num]	2003	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
City	NNP	N[nam]	city	I-LOC
banned	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	ban	O
smoking	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	smoking	O
indoors	NNS	N[nom]	indoor	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Last	JJ	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/S[dcl]/S[dcl]	last	I-DAT
year	NN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	year	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
prohibited	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP/NP	prohibit	O
restaurants	NNS	N[nom]	restaurant	O
from	IN	PP/S[ng]\NP	from	O
using	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	use	O
trans	NNS	N[nom]/N[nom]	tran	O
fats	NNS	N[nom]	fat	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
food	NN	N[nom]	food	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Now	RB	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	now	O
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
New	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	new	I-LOC
York	NNP	N[nam]	york	I-LOC
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
requiring	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[to]\NP/NP	require	O
many	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	many	O
restaurants	NNS	N[nom]	restaurant	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
publish	VB	S[b]\NP	publish	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
post	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	post	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
calorie	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	calorie	O
content	NN	N[nom]	content	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
their	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	their	O
foods	NNS	N[nom]	food	O
,	,	COMMA	,	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
help	VB	S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP	help	O
combat	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	combat	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
growing	VBG	N[nom]/N[nom]	grow	O
"	LQU	N[nom]/N[nom]	"	O
obesity	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	obesity	O
epidemic	NN	N[nom]	epidemic	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O
"	LQU	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	"	O

City	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	city	I-LOC
officials	NNS	N[nom]	official	O
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
this	DT	NP	this	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
their	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	their	O
way	NN	N[nom]	way	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
fight	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	fight	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
obesity	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	obesity	O
epidemic	NN	N[nom]	epidemic	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
other	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	other	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.	I-LOC
cities	NNS	N[nom]	city	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
following	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	follow	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
lead	NN	N[nom]	lead	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
Paige	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	paige	I-LOC
Kollock	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	kollock	I-LOC
reports	NNS	N[nom]	report	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
New	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	new	I-LOC
York	NNP	N[nam]	york	I-LOC
.	.	NP\NP	.	O



