Gunners	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	gunner	O
Football	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	football	I-ORG
Club	NNP	N[nam]	club	I-ORG
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
moved	VBN	S[pt]\NP	move	O
to	TO	S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
top	NN	N[nom]	top	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Zimbabwe	NNP	N[nam]	zimbabwe	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	I-ORG
Premier	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	premier	I-ORG
Soccer	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	soccer	I-ORG
League	NNP	N[nam]	league	I-ORG
,	,	S[dcl]/NP/S[dcl]/NP	,	O
displacing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	displace	O
Dynamos	NNP	N[nam]	dynamo	O
which	WDT	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	which	O
had	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
headed	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	head	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
league	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	league	O
table	NN	N[nom]	table	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
some	DT	NP	some	O
seeks	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	seek	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

But	CC	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	but	O
Gunners	NNS	N[nom]	gunner	O
with	IN	NP\NP/NP	with	O
41	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	41	O
points	NNS	N[nom]	point	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
just	RB	N[num]/N[num]	just	O
one	CD	N[num]	one	O
up	RP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	up	O
on	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	on	O
Dynamos	NNS	N[nom]	dynamo	O
with	IN	NP\NP/NP	with	O
40	CD	N[num]	40	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Gunners	NNPS	N[nam]/N[nam]	gunner	O
Coach	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	coach	I-PER
Moses	NNPS	N[nam]/N[nam]	mose	I-PER
“	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	“	I-PER
Bambo	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	bambo	I-PER
”	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	”	I-PER
Chunga	NNP	N[nam]	chunga	I-PER
told	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[em]/NP	tell	O
reporter	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	reporter	O
Marvellous	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	marvellous	O
Mhlanga-Nyahuye	NNP	N[nam]	mhlanga-nyahuye	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	I-ORG
Studio	NNP	N[nam]	studio	I-ORG
7	CD	N[nam]\N[nam]	7	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
Zimbabwe	NNP	N[nam]	zimbabwe	I-ORG
that	IN	S[em]/S[dcl]	that	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
team	NN	N[nom]	team	O
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
do	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	do	O
all	DT	NP	all	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
can	MD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	can	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
capture	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	capture	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
title	NN	N[nom]	title	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

More	JJR	N[nom]/N[nom]	more	O
reports	NNS	N[nom]	report	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	I-ORG
Studio7	NNP	N[nam]	studio7	I-ORG
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	I-ORG
Zimbabwe	NNP	N[nam]	zimbabwe	I-ORG
.	.	NP\NP	.	O

.	.	NP	.	O

.	.	NP	.	O



