Two	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	two	O
astronauts	NNS	N[nom]	astronaut	O
have	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
resumed	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	resume	O
work	NN	N[nom]	work	O
outside	IN	NP\NP/NP	outside	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	I-LOC
International	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	international	I-LOC
Space	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	space	I-LOC
Station	NNP	N[nam]	station	I-LOC
on	IN	NP\NP/NP	on	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
new	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	new	O
European	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	european	O
science	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	science	O
laboratory	NN	N[nom]	laboratory	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Rex	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	rex	I-PER
Walheim	NNP	N[nam]	walheim	I-PER
and	CC	CONJ	and	I-PER
Stanley	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	stanley	I-PER
Love	NNP	N[nam]	love	I-PER
began	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	begin	O
their	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	their	O
spacewalk	NN	N[nom]	spacewalk	O
Friday	NNP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	friday	I-DAT
morning	NN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	morning	I-TIM
,	,	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	,	O
installing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	install	O
science	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	science	O
experiments	NNS	N[nom]	experiment	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
including	VBG	NP\NP/NP	include	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
solar	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	solar	O
monitor	NN	N[nom]	monitor	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
to	TO	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
exterior	NN	N[nom]	exterior	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Columbus	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	columbus	O
lab	NN	N[nom]	lab	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

It	PRP	NP	it	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
third	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	third	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
final	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	final	O
spacewalk	NN	N[nom]	spacewalk	O
during	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	during	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.	I-LOC
shuttle	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	shuttle	O
Atlantis	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	atlanti	O
mission	NN	N[nom]	mission	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
orbital	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	orbital	O
outpost	NN	N[nom]	outpost	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Walheim	NNP	N[nam]	walheim	I-PER
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
Love	NNP	N[nam]	love	I-PER
installed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	install	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
European	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	european	I-ORG
Space	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	space	I-ORG
Agency	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	agency	I-ORG
lab	NN	N[nom]	lab	O
Monday	NNP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	monday	I-DAT
with	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	with	O
help	NN	N[nom]	help	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
crew	NN	N[nom]	crew	O
inside	IN	NP\NP/NP	inside	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
space	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	space	O
station	NN	N[nom]	station	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Atlantis	NNP	N[nam]	atlanti	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
set	VBN	S[pss]\NP/S[to]\NP	set	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
return	VB	S[b]\NP	return	O
to	TO	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	to	O
Earth	NNP	N[nam]	earth	I-LOC
next	JJ	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	next	I-DAT
week	NN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	week	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



