U.S.	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.	I-LOC
legislators	NNS	N[nom]	legislator	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
North	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	north	O
Korean	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	korean	O
activists	NNS	N[nom]	activist	O
have	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
recounted	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	recount	O
stories	NNS	N[nom]	story	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
injustice	NN	N[nom]	injustice	O
they	PRP	NP	they	O
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
China	NNP	N[nam]	china	I-LOC
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
inflicted	VBN	S[pt]\NP/PP	inflict	O
on	IN	PP/NP	on	O
refugees	NNS	N[nom]	refugee	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

At	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	at	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
news	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	news	O
conference	NN	N[nom]	conference	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Washington	NNP	N[nam]	washington	I-LOC
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
group	NN	N[nom]	group	O
called	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[to]\NP/PP	call	O
on	IN	PP/NP	on	O
world	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	world	O
leaders	NNS	N[nom]	leader	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
boycott	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	boycott	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
2008	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	2008	I-DAT
Olympics	NNPS	N[nom]/N[nom]	olympics	O
opening	VBG	N[nom]/N[nom]	open	O
ceremonies	NNS	N[nom]	ceremony	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

They	PRP	NP	they	O
accused	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP/NP	accuse	O
China	NNP	N[nam]	china	I-LOC
of	IN	PP/NP	of	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
"	RQU	N[nom]/N[nom]	"	O
record	NN	N[nom]	record	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
shame	NN	N[nom]	shame	O
"	RQU	NP\NP	"	O
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
its	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	its	O
treatment	NN	N[nom]	treatment	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
North	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]	north	O
Korean	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	korean	O
defectors	NNS	N[nom]	defector	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
tried	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[to]\NP	try	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
flee	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	flee	O
repression	NN	N[nom]	repression	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	O
Carolyn	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	carolyn	I-PER
Presutti	NNP	N[nam]	presuttus	I-PER
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	have	O
our	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	our	O
story	NN	N[nom]	story	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
perspective	NN	N[nom]	perspective	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
defector	NN	N[nom]	defector	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



