Reports	NNS	N[nom]	report	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
Rangoon	NNP	N[nam]	rangoon	I-ORG
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
military	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	military	O
government	NN	N[nom]	government	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Burma	NNP	N[nam]	burma	I-LOC
quietly	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	quietly	O
sentenced	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP/NP	sentence	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
Buddhist	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	buddhist	O
monk	NN	N[nom]	monk	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
seven	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	seven	O
years	NNS	N[nom]	year	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
prison	NN	N[nom]	prison	O
during	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	during	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
visit	NN	N[nom]	visit	O
this	DT	NP\NP/N[nom]	this	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
United	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	united	I-ORG
Nations	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	nation	I-ORG
human	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	human	O
rights	NNS	N[nom]/N[nom]	rights	O
envoy	NN	N[nom]	envoy	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

A	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
lawyer	NN	N[nom]	lawyer	O
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[em]	say	O
Saturday	NNP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	saturday	I-DAT
that	IN	S[em]/S[dcl]	that	O
U	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	u	I-ORG
Gaw	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	gaw	I-ORG
Thita	NNP	N[nam]	thita	I-ORG
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
arrested	VBN	S[pss]\NP	arrest	O
last	JJ	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP	last	I-DAT
August	NNP	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP	august	I-DAT
as	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/S[dcl]	as	O
he	PRP	NP	he	O
returned	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	return	O
from	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	from	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
trip	NN	N[nom]	trip	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
Taiwan	NNP	N[nam]	taiwan	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

He	PRP	NP	he	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
convicted	VBN	S[pss]\NP	convict	O
at	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	at	O
Burma	NNP	N[nam]	burma	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	O
notorious	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	notorious	O
Insein	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	insein	I-ORG
Prison	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	prison	I-ORG
Wednesday	NNP	N[nam]	wednesday	I-DAT
on	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	on	O
three	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	three	O
charges	NNS	N[nom]	charge	O
including	VBG	NP\NP/NP	include	O
unlawful	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	unlawful	O
association	NN	N[nom]	association	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
lawyer	NN	N[nom]	lawyer	O
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
monk	NN	N[nom]	monk	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
also	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	also	O
convicted	VBN	S[pss]\NP/PP	convict	O
of	IN	PP/S[ng]\NP	of	O
failing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[to]\NP	fail	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
declare	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	declare	O
possession	NN	N[nom]	possession	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
currency	NN	N[nom]	currency	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
for	IN	PP/NP	for	O
violation	NN	N[nom]	violation	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
immigration	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	immigration	O
laws	NNS	N[nom]	law	O
for	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	for	O
taking	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	take	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
trip	NN	N[nom]	trip	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



