President	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	president	O
Bush	NNP	N[nam]	bush	I-PER
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
called	VBN	S[pt]\NP/S[to]\NP/NP	call	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
Indonesian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	indonesian	O
counterpart	NN	N[nom]	counterpart	O
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
Susilo	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	susilo	I-ORG
Bambang	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	bambang	I-ORG
Yudhoyono	NNP	N[nam]	yudhoyono	I-ORG
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
discuss	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	discuss	O
security	NN	N[nom]	security	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
trade	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	trade	O
issues	NNS	N[nom]	issue	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
two	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	two	O
presidents	NNS	N[nom]	president	O
also	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	also	O
expressed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	express	O
hope	NN	N[nom]	hope	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
positive	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	positive	O
outcome	NN	N[nom]	outcome	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
talks	NNS	N[nom]	talk	O
by	IN	NP\NP/NP	by	O
trade	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	trade	O
ministers	NNS	N[nom]	minister	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
developing	VBG	N[nom]/N[nom]	develop	O
countries	NNS	N[nom]	country	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Jakarta	NNP	N[nam]	jakarta	I-LOC
later	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	later	I-DAT
this	DT	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/N[nom]	this	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



