A	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
press	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	press	O
spokesman	NN	N[nom]	spokesman	O
for	IN	NP\NP/NP	for	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	u.s.	I-ORG
Trade	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	trade	O
Representative	NNP	N[nam]	representative	I-ORG
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	I-ORG
Neena	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	neena	I-ORG
Moorjani	NNP	N[nam]	moorjanus	I-ORG
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
delays	NNS	N[nom]	delay	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	be	O
common	JJ	S[adj]\NP	common	O
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
free	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	free	O
trade	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	trade	O
talks	NNS	N[nom]	talk	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Moorjani	NNP	N[nam]	moorjanus	I-ORG
would	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	would	O
not	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	not	O
comment	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	comment	O
on	IN	PP/NP	on	O
any	DT	NP/N[nom]	any	O
link	NN	N[nom]	link	O
between	IN	NP\NP/NP	between	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
political	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	political	O
storm	NN	N[nom]	storm	O
over	IN	NP\NP/NP	over	O
DP	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	dp	I-ORG
World	NNP	N[nam]	world	I-ORG
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
delay	NN	N[nom]	delay	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
talks	NNS	N[nom]	talk	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

But	CC	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	but	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
major	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	major	O
business	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	business	O
group	NN	N[nom]	group	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
controversy	NN	N[nom]	controversy	O
over	IN	NP\NP/NP	over	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
ports	NNS	N[nom]/N[nom]	port	O
deal	NN	N[nom]	deal	O
could	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	could	O
hurt	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	hurt	O
Washington	NNP	N[nam]	washington	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
ability	NN	N[nom]	ability	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
promote	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	promote	O
free	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	free	O
trade	NN	N[nom]	trade	O
around	IN	NP\NP/NP	around	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
world	NN	N[nom]	world	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
investment	NN	N[nom]	investment	O
here	RB	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	here	O
at	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	at	O
home	NN	N[nom]	home	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	u.s.	I-ORG
Chamber	NNP	N[nam]	chamber	I-ORG
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	I-ORG
Commerce	NNP	N[nam]	commerce	I-ORG
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
foreigners	NNS	N[nom]	foreigner	O
invest	VBP	S[dcl]\NP	invest	O
$	$	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/N[num]	$	O
80	CD	N[num]/N[num]	80	O
billion	CD	N[num]	billion	O
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
United	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	united	I-LOC
States	NNPS	N[nam]	state	I-LOC
a	DT	NP\NP/N[nom]	a	I-DAT
year	NN	N[nom]	year	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	,	O
creating	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	create	O
five	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	five	O
million	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	million	O
jobs	NNS	N[nom]	job	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



