A	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
New	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	new	I-LOC
York	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	york	I-LOC
jury	NN	N[nom]	jury	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	have	O
convicted	VBN	S[pss]\NP	convict	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
Yemeni	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	yemenus	I-ORG
cleric	NN	N[nom]	cleric	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
assistant	NN	N[nom]	assistant	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
charges	NNS	N[nom]	charge	O
of	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	of	O
conspiring	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[to]\NP	conspire	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
fund	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	fund	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Islamic	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	islamic	O
terror	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	terror	O
groups	NNS	N[nom]	group	O
al-Qaida	JJ	S[adj]\NP	al-qaida	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
Hamas	NNP	S[adj]\NP	hama	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Sheik	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	sheik	I-PER
Mohammed	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mohammed	I-PER
Ali	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	alus	I-PER
Hassan	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	hassan	I-PER
al-Moayad	NNP	N[nam]	al-moayad	I-PER
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
Mohammed	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mohammed	I-PER
Yahya	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	yahya	I-PER
Zayed	NNP	N[nam]	zayed	I-PER
were	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
arrested	VBN	S[pss]\NP/PP	arrest	O
in	IN	PP/NP	in	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
FBI	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	fbus	I-ORG
operation	NN	N[nom]	operation	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Frankfurt	NNP	N[nam]	frankfurt	I-LOC
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
Germany	NNP	N[nam]	germany	I-LOC
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
2003	CD	N[num]	2003	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Undercover	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	undercover	O
agents	NNS	N[nom]	agent	O
videotaped	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP/NP	videotape	O
them	PRP	NP	them	O
offering	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[to]\NP	offer	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
send	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	send	O
money	NN	N[nom]	money	O
to	TO	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
terror	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	terror	O
groups	NNS	N[nom]	group	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Their	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	their	O
lawyers	NNS	N[nom]	lawyer	O
called	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP/NP	call	O
them	PRP	NP	them	O
victims	NNS	N[nom]	victim	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
entrapment	NN	N[nom]	entrapment	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
jury	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	jury	O
Thursday	NNP	N[nam]	thursday	I-DAT
also	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	also	O
found	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	find	O
al-Moyad	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	al-moyad	O
guilty	NN	N[nom]	guilty	O
of	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	of	O
actually	RB	S[ng]\NP/S[ng]\NP	actually	O
providing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/PP/NP	provide	O
support	NN	N[nom]	support	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
Hamas	NNP	N[nam]	hama	I-LOC
,	,	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	,	O
but	CC	CONJ	but	O
acquitted	VBN	S[dcl]\NP/NP	acquit	O
him	PRP	NP	him	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
charges	NNS	N[nom]	charge	O
of	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	of	O
sending	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	send	O
such	JJ	NP/NP	such	O
backing	NN	N[nom]	backing	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
al-Qaida	NNP	N[nam]	al-qaida	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



