This	DT	NP/N[nom]	this	O
isolated	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	isolated	O
island	NN	N[nom]	island	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
named	VBN	S[pss]\NP/PP	name	O
for	IN	PP/NP	for	O
John	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	john	I-PER
CLIPPERTON	NNP	N[nam]	clipperton	I-PER
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
pirate	NN	N[nom]	pirate	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
made	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP/NP	make	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
hideout	NN	N[nom]	hideout	O
early	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/PP	early	I-DAT
in	IN	PP/NP	in	I-DAT
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	I-DAT
18th	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	18th	I-DAT
century	NN	N[nom]	century	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Annexed	VBN	S[pss]\NP	annex	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
France	NNP	N[nam]	france	I-ORG
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
1855	CD	N[num]	1855	I-DAT
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
seized	VBN	S[pss]\NP	seize	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
Mexico	NNP	N[nam]	mexico	I-ORG
in	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	in	O
1897	CD	N[num]	1897	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Arbitration	NNP	N[nam]	arbitration	O
eventually	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	eventually	O
awarded	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP/NP	award	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
island	NN	N[nom]	island	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
France	NNP	N[nam]	france	I-ORG
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
which	WDT	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	which	O
took	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	take	O
possession	NN	N[nom]	possession	O
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
1935	CD	N[num]	1935	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



