President	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	president	O
Bush	NNP	N[nam]	bush	I-PER
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
United	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	united	I-LOC
States	NNPS	N[nam]	state	I-LOC
remains	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	remain	O
committed	JJ	S[adj]\NP/PP	committed	O
to	TO	PP/S[ng]\NP	to	O
helping	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	help	O
victims	NNS	N[nom]	victim	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Indian	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	indian	I-LOC
Ocean	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	ocean	I-LOC
tsunami	NNP	N[nam]	tsunami	O
rebuild	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	rebuild	O
their	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	their	O
lives	NNS	N[nom]	life	O
.	.	S[b]\S[b]	.	O

In	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	in	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
statement	NN	N[nom]	statement	O
issued	VBN	S[pss]\NP	issue	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
White	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	white	I-ORG
House	NNP	N[nam]	house	I-ORG
as	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/S[dcl]	as	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
President	NNP	N[nam]	president	O
left	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	leave	O
for	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	for	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
vacation	NN	N[nom]	vacation	O
at	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	at	O
his	PRP$	NP/N[nom]	his	O
Texas	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	texa	I-LOC
ranch	NN	N[nom]	ranch	I-LOC
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
Mr.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mr.	I-LOC
Bush	NNP	N[nam]	bush	I-PER
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
thoughts	NNS	N[nom]	thought	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
prayers	NNS	N[nom]	prayer	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
American	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	american	O
people	NNS	N[nom]	people	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/PP	be	O
with	IN	PP/NP	with	O
those	DT	NP	those	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
suffered	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP	suffer	O
from	IN	PP/NP	from	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
tragedy	NN	N[nom]	tragedy	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

He	PRP	NP	he	O
also	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	also	O
praised	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	praise	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
efforts	NNS	N[nom]	effort	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
generosity	NN	N[nom]	generosity	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.	I-LOC
armed	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	armed	O
services	NNS	N[nom]	service	O
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
relief	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	relief	O
workers	NNS	N[nom]	worker	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
all	PDT	NP/NP	all	O
those	DT	NP	those	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
contributed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP	contribute	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
relief	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	relief	O
effort	NN	N[nom]	effort	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



