Palestinian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	palestinian	O
officials	NNS	N[nom]	official	O
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
newly-elected	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	newly-elected	O
Palestinian	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	palestinian	O
President	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	president	O
Mahmoud	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mahmoud	I-PER
Abbas	NNP	N[nam]	abba	I-PER
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
meet	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	meet	O
with	IN	PP/NP	with	O
militants	NNS	N[nom]	militant	O
in	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Gaza	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	gaza	I-LOC
Strip	NNP	N[nam]	strip	I-LOC
later	RB	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	later	I-DAT
this	DT	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/N[nom]	this	I-DAT
week	NN	N[nom]	week	I-DAT
in	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	in	O
an	DT	NP/N[nom]	an	O
attempt	NN	N[nom]	attempt	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
persuade	VB	S[b]\NP/S[to]\NP/NP	persuade	O
them	PRP	NP	them	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
end	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	end	O
attacks	NNS	N[nom]	attack	O
against	IN	NP\NP/NP	against	O
Israel	NNP	N[nam]	israel	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Palestinian	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	palestinian	O
Foreign	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	foreign	O
Minister	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	minister	O
Nabil	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	nabil	I-PER
Shaath	NNP	N[nam]	shaath	I-PER
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
Mr.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mr.	I-PER
Abbas	NNP	N[nam]	abba	I-PER
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
make	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	make	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
trip	NN	N[nom]	trip	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
Gaza	NNP	N[nam]	gaza	I-LOC
Wednesday	NNP	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	wednesday	I-DAT
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
press	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	press	O
militant	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	militant	O
groups	NNS	N[nom]	group	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
agree	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	agree	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
cease-fire	NN	N[nom]	cease-fire	O
that	WDT	NP\NP/S[dcl]/NP	that	O
Palestinians	NNPS	N[nam]	palestinian	O
say	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/NP/S[dcl]\NP	say	O
must	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	must	O
be	VB	S[b]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
reciprocated	VBN	S[pss]\NP	reciprocate	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
Israel	NNP	N[nam]	israel	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
minister	NN	N[nom]	minister	O
says	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Palestinian	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	palestinian	O
leader	NN	N[nom]	leader	O
will	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	will	O
also	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	also	O
try	VB	S[b]\NP/S[to]\NP	try	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
persuade	VB	S[b]\NP/S[to]\NP/NP	persuade	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
groups	NNS	N[nom]	group	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
participate	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	participate	O
in	IN	PP/NP	in	O
parliamentary	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	parliamentary	O
elections	NNS	N[nom]	election	O
on	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	on	O
July	NNP	N[num]/N[num]	july	I-DAT
17	CD	N[num]	17	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Mr.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mr.	I-PER
Abbas	NNP	N[nam]	abba	I-PER
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
denounced	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	denounce	O
violence	NN	N[nom]	violence	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
both	DT	NP/N[nom]	both	O
sides	NNS	N[nom]	side	O
for	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	for	O
undermining	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	undermine	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
peace	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	peace	O
process	NN	N[nom]	process	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



