All	DT	NP/N[nom]	all	O
economic	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	economic	O
activity	NN	N[nom]	activity	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
concentrated	VBN	S[pss]\NP	concentrate	O
on	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	on	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
largest	JJS	N[nom]/N[nom]	largest	O
island	NN	N[nom]	island	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
Diego	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	diego	I-LOC
Garcia	NNP	N[nam]	garcium	I-LOC
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
where	WRB	NP\NP/S[dcl]	where	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
joint	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	joint	O
UK-US	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	uk-us	O
military	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	military	O
facility	NN	N[nom]	facility	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
located	VBN	S[pss]\NP	locate	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Construction	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	construction	O
projects	NNS	N[nom]	project	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
various	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	various	O
services	NNS	N[nom]	service	O
needed	VBN	S[pss]\NP/S[to]\NP	need	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
support	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	support	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
military	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	military	O
installation	NN	N[nom]	installation	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
performed	VBN	S[pss]\NP	perform	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
military	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	military	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
contract	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	contract	O
employees	NNS	N[nom]	employee	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
UK	NNP	N[nam]	uk	I-ORG
,	,	COMMA	,	O
Mauritius	NNP	N[nam]	mauritius	I-LOC
,	,	COMMA	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Philippines	NNPS	N[nam]	philippine	I-LOC
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
US	NNP	N[nam]	us	I-ORG
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

There	EX	NP	there	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
no	DT	NP/N[nom]	no	O
industrial	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	industrial	O
or	CC	CONJ	or	O
agricultural	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	agricultural	O
activities	NNS	N[nom]	activity	O
on	IN	NP\NP/NP	on	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
islands	NNS	N[nom]	island	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
territory	NN	N[nom]	territory	O
earns	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	earn	O
foreign	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	foreign	O
exchange	NN	N[nom]	exchange	O
by	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	by	O
selling	VBG	S[ng]\NP/NP	sell	O
fishing	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	fishing	O
licenses	NNS	N[nom]	licens	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
postage	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	postage	O
stamps	NNS	N[nom]	stamp	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



