A	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
British	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	british	O
Royal	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	royal	I-ORG
Air	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	air	I-ORG
Force	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	force	I-ORG
doctor	NN	N[nom]	doctor	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
appeared	VBN	S[pt]\NP	appear	O
in	IN	S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP/NP	in	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
military	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	military	O
court	NN	N[nom]	court	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
pleaded	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	plead	O
not	RB	S[adj]\NP/S[adj]\NP	not	O
guilty	JJ	S[adj]\NP/PP	guilty	O
to	TO	PP/NP	to	O
five	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	five	O
charges	NNS	N[nom]	charge	O
of	IN	NP\NP/S[ng]\NP	of	O
failing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[to]\NP	fail	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
comply	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	comply	O
with	IN	PP/NP	with	O
orders	NNS	N[nom]	order	O
after	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/S[ng]\NP	after	O
refusing	VBG	S[ng]\NP/S[to]\NP	refuse	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
go	VB	S[b]\NP	go	O
to	TO	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	to	O
Iraq	NNP	N[nam]	iraq	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Flight	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	flight	I-ORG
Lieutenant	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	lieutenant	I-ORG
Malcolm	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	malcolm	I-ORG
Kendall-Smith	NNP	N[nam]	kendall-smith	I-ORG
refused	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[to]\NP	refuse	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
attend	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	attend	O
training	NN	N[nom]	training	O
in	IN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/NP	in	O
advance	NN	N[nom]	advance	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
deployment	NN	N[nom]	deployment	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
Basra	NNP	N[nam]	basra	I-LOC
last	JJ	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	last	I-DAT
year	NN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	year	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

He	PRP	NP	he	O
said	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	say	O
he	PRP	NP	he	O
believed	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]	believe	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
2003	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	2003	I-DAT
U.S.-led	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.-led	I-DAT
invasion	NN	N[nom]	invasion	I-DAT
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	I-DAT
Iraq	NNP	N[nam]	iraq	I-LOC
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	be	O
illegal	JJ	S[adj]\NP	illegal	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
prosecutor	NN	N[nom]	prosecutor	O
told	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	tell	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
court	NN	N[nom]	court	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
presence	NN	N[nom]	presence	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
British	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	british	O
forces	NNS	N[nom]	force	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
Iraq	NNP	N[nam]	iraq	I-LOC
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[adj]\NP	be	O
not	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	not	O
unlawful	JJ	S[adj]\NP	unlawful	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
officer	NN	N[nom]	officer	O
had	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
already	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	already	O
completed	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	complete	O
tours	NNS	N[nom]	tour	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
duty	NN	N[nom]	duty	O
in	IN	S[pt]\NP\S[pt]\NP/NP	in	O
Iraq	NNP	N[nam]	iraq	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



