The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
beginning	NN	N[nom]	beginning	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
traditional	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	traditional	O
Chinese	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	chinese	O
medicine	NN	N[nom]	medicine	O
dates	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	date	O
back	RB	S[adj]\NP/S[adj]\NP	back	O
more	JJR	S[adj]\NP	more	O
than	IN	N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]/N[nom]\S[adj]\NP	than	O
2,000	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	2,000	O
years	NNS	N[nom]	year	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

But	CC	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	but	O
it	PRP	NP	it	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[em]/PP	be	O
not	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	not	O
until	IN	PP/NP	until	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	I-DAT
17th	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	17th	I-DAT
century	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	century	I-DAT
A.D.	NNP	N[nam]	a.d.	I-DAT
that	IN	S[em]/S[dcl]	that	O
westerners	NNS	N[nom]	westerner	O
first	RB	S[dcl]\NP/S[dcl]\NP	first	O
heard	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/PP	hear	O
about	IN	PP/NP	about	O
those	DT	NP/N[nom]	those	O
ancient	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	ancient	O
treatments	NNS	N[nom]	treatment	O
from	IN	NP\NP/NP	from	O
Jesuit	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	jesuit	I-ORG
missionaries	NNS	N[nom]	missionary	O
who	WP	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	who	O
traveled	VBD	S[dcl]\NP	travel	O
to	TO	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	to	O
Asia	NNP	N[nam]	asia	I-LOC
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	O
Melinda	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	melinda	I-PER
Smith	NNP	N[nam]	smith	I-PER
reports	VBZ	S[dcl]\S[dcl]\NP	report	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]\S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



