In	IN	S[dcl]/S[dcl]/NP	in	O
31	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	31	O
cities	NNS	N[nom]	city	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
towns	NNS	N[nom]	town	O
across	IN	NP\NP/NP	across	O
America	NNP	N[nam]	america	I-LOC
,	,	S[dcl]/S[dcl]	,	O
people	NNS	N[nom]	people	O
are	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[ng]\NP	be	O
touching	VBG	S[ng]\NP	touch	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
even	RB	S[ng]\NP/S[ng]\NP	even	O
riding	VBG	S[ng]\NP	ride	O
in	IN	S[ng]\NP\S[ng]\NP/NP	in	O
what	WP	NP/S[dcl]/NP	what	O
some	DT	NP	some	O
might	MD	S[dcl]\NP/S[b]\NP	might	O
call	VB	S[b]\NP/NP/NP	call	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
'	POS	N[nom]/N[nom]	'	O
cars	NNS	N[nom]	car	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
future	NN	N[nom]	future	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O
'	POS	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	'	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
U.S.	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	u.s.	I-ORG
Departments	NNS	N[nom]	department	I-ORG
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	I-ORG
Energy	NNP	N[nam]	energy	I-ORG
and	CC	CONJ	and	I-ORG
Transportation	NNP	N[nam]	transportation	I-ORG
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
The	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	I-ORG
California	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	californium	I-ORG
Fuel	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	fuel	I-ORG
Cell	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	cell	I-ORG
Partnership	NNP	N[nam]	partnership	I-ORG
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
National	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	national	I-ORG
Hydrogen	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	hydrogen	I-ORG
Association	NNP	N[nam]	association	I-ORG
as	RB	CONJ/CONJ	as	O
well	RB	CONJ/CONJ	well	O
as	IN	CONJ	as	O
nine	CD	N[nom]/N[nom]	nine	O
auto	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	auto	O
manufacturers	NNS	N[nom]	manufacturer	O
have	VBP	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
put	VBN	S[pt]\NP/PP/NP	put	O
several	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	several	O
hydrogen-fueled	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	hydrogen-fueled	O
cars	NNS	N[nom]	car	O
on	IN	PP/NP	on	O
tour	NN	N[nom]	tour	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

VOA	NNP	N[nam]	voa	I-ORG
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	O
Paul	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	paul	I-PER
Sisco	NNP	N[nam]	sisco	I-PER
caught	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	catch	O
up	RP	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	up	O
with	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	with	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
show	NN	N[nom]	show	O
recently	RB	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP	recently	O
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
Washington	NNP	N[nam]	washington	I-LOC
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
DC	NNP	N[nam]	dc	O
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
files	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	file	O
this	DT	NP/N[nom]	this	O
report	NN	N[nom]	report	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



