Thailand	NNP	N[nam]	thailand	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nam]\NP	's	O
military-backed	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	military-backed	O
interim	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	interim	O
prime	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	prime	O
minister	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	minister	O
Surayud	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	surayud	I-PER
Chulanont	NNP	N[nam]	chulanont	I-PER
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/PP	be	O
in	IN	PP/NP	in	O
Indonesia	NNP	N[nam]	indonesium	I-LOC
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
meet	VB	S[b]\NP/PP	meet	O
with	IN	PP/NP	with	O
President	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	president	O
Susilo	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	susilo	O
Bambang	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	bambang	I-PER
Yudhoyono	NNP	N[nam]	yudhoyono	I-PER
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Mr.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mr.	I-LOC
Surayud	NNP	N[nam]	surayud	I-PER
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
visit	NN	N[nom]	visit	O
Saturday	NNP	N[nam]	saturday	I-DAT
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/NP	be	O
the	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
latest	JJS	N[nom]	latest	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
flurry	NN	N[nom]	flurry	O
of	IN	NP\NP/NP	of	O
introductory	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	introductory	O
diplomatic	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	diplomatic	O
trips	NNS	N[nom]	trip	O
to	TO	NP\NP/NP	to	O
Thailand	NNP	N[nam]	thailand	I-LOC
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
neighbors	NNS	N[nom]	neighbor	O
following	VBG	NP\NP/NP	follow	O
last	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	last	I-DAT
month	NN	N[nom]	month	I-DAT
's	POS	NP/N[nom]\NP	's	O
coup	NN	N[nom]	coup	O
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

The	DT	NP/N[nom]	the	O
Thai	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	thaus	O
interim	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	interim	O
prime	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	prime	O
minister	NN	N[nom]	minister	O
has	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pt]\NP	have	O
visited	VBN	S[pt]\NP/NP	visit	O
Malaysia	NNP	N[nam]	malaysium	I-LOC
,	,	CONJ[app]	,	O
Laos	NNP	N[nam]	lao	I-LOC
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
Cambodia	NNP	N[nam]	cambodium	I-LOC
and	CC	CONJ	and	O
is	VBZ	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
scheduled	VBN	S[pss]\NP/S[to]\NP	schedule	O
to	TO	S[to]\NP/S[b]\NP	to	O
meet	VB	S[b]\NP/NP	meet	O
leaders	NNS	N[nom]	leader	O
in	IN	NP\NP/NP	in	O
the	DT	NP/N[nam]	the	O
Philippines	NNPS	N[nam]	philippine	I-ORG
and	CC	CONJ	and	I-ORG
Vietnam	NNP	N[nam]	vietnam	I-ORG
next	JJ	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP/S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	next	I-DAT
week	NN	S[b]\NP\S[b]\NP	week	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O

Mr.	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	mr.	I-LOC
Surayud	NNP	N[nam]	surayud	I-PER
,	,	COMMA	,	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
former	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	former	O
army	NN	N[nom]/N[nom]	army	O
general	NN	N[nom]	general	O
,	,	NP\NP	,	O
was	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/S[pss]\NP	be	O
appointed	VBN	S[pss]\NP	appoint	O
by	IN	S[pss]\NP\S[pss]\NP/NP	by	O
a	DT	NP/N[nom]	a	O
Thai	NNP	N[nom]/N[nom]	thaus	O
military	JJ	N[nom]/N[nom]	military	O
council	NN	N[nom]	council	O
that	WDT	NP\NP/S[dcl]\NP	that	O
ousted	VBD	S[dcl]\NP/NP	oust	O
former	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	former	O
prime	JJ	N[nam]/N[nam]	prime	O
minister	NN	N[nam]/N[nam]	minister	O
Thaksin	NNP	N[nam]/N[nam]	thaksin	I-PER
Shinawatra	NNP	N[nam]	shinawatra	I-PER
in	IN	S[dcl]\NP\S[dcl]\NP/NP	in	O
September	NNP	N[nam]	september	I-DAT
.	.	S[dcl]\S[dcl]	.	O



